unigamesity.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Unigamesity

Unigamesity is committed to protecting you and your family’s personal information and privacy when using Unigamesity’s (the Website) services. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide through the Unigamesity website.

 **Affiliate Information**  
Unigamesity is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com products. We may also link to various other affiliate networks or programs.

 **Collecting your Personal Information**  
If you wish to do so, you can remain anonymous for the entire duration of your visit on the Unigamesity website. However, we do require personal information from you in a few specific circumstances. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (usually your name and e-mail address). Generally, this information is requested when posting comments on the website, when you are asked to register before entering a contest, if you subscribe to one of our properties or elect to participate in a survey.

Unigamesity allows third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements within the Website. These third-party servers or networks use technology to send advertisements, directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. However, no other Personal Information (such as name, e-mail, address etc) is collected or required in such circumstances. When it comes to Google advertising, users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/). To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

You need to acknowledge that, whenever you disclose information in public areas on the Website, such as comment areas on the Website, the information in the comment you post becomes public. You should never share personal data (including, but not limited to usernames and passwords) in the public comments you post on our website. We will do our best to remove such information posted on our website, but it is ultimately your responsibility.

 **Use of your Personal Information**  
Unigamesity will use the Personal Information you submit to (1) make sure we credit your work correctly in case of user submitted content; and (2) to correctly send you prizes you might win in contests held on the Website. However, when you submit User Content, we will only share the name you allow us to share (which can also be a nickname or alias). We will never send you unwanted e-mails, messages or promotional features. We will never share, rent or sell your e-mail address to any other company or third party.

 **Email Correspondence**  
Unigamesity staff will respond to e-mails sent directly to them via the contact form or other ways of contact. The sender’s e-mail address will never be shared and we will not use your e-mail address to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail.

 **How we protect information collected from you**  
We show great interest in confidentiality. Unigamesity is a spam free zone. Also, we will never share your Personal Information or e-mail address to third parties without your prior express consent. Any statistics that we might offer to our advertisement networks does not include any personal identifying information about any individual user. We do our best efforts to protect the security of your personal information.

 **Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post a notice about the changes here so make sure to visit it regularly.

This Privacy Policy has been updated today, 20th of April, 2016.
